Stuart Gerry Brown Papers
Stuart Gerry Brown Papers
- Writings
  - Reports
    - of Special Joint Committee of Syracuse University, LeMoyne College and the Onondaga County American Legion, S.G. Brown with others, typescript reproduction (Box 21)
  - Short pieces re: Adlai E. Stevenson, typescript and typescript copy (Box 21)
  - for Adlai E. Stevenson
    - Report on Democratic Record on Corruption & Integrity in Government, 1952; draft A, holo.; draft B, typescript copy; correspondence (Box 21)
    - Speeches
      - Drafts and suggestions, 1956-1963; typescript and typescript copy (Box 21)
      - Research material, includes holograph notes and typescript suggestions (Box 21)
      - I - Local and State Governments, draft A, holo.; draft B typescript copy (Box 21)
      - II - On Integrity in Government, draft A, holo.; draft B, typescript rev.; draft C, typescript rev.; draft D typescript copy (Box 21)
      - III - On Corruption, 1952; holograph notes; draft A, holo.; draft B, typescript; correspondence (Box 21)
      - IV - On the Liberal Tradition, 1952; draft A, holo.; draft B, typescript rev.; draft C, typescript copy; correspondence (Box 21)
      - V - Paragraphs on Economic Prosperity, 1952; draft A, typescript rev.; draft B, typescript copy; correspondence (Box 22)
      - VI - Program to Promote Integrity in Government, 1952; draft A, holo.; draft B, typescript copy; correspondence (Box 22)
      - Reply to Eisenhower Speech of Oct 20, 1952, Bridgeport, Conn., draft A, typescript rev.; draft B, typescript copy (Box 22)
      - Reply to Eisenhower Speech of Oct 21, 1952, Boston, Mass., draft A, typescript rev.; draft B, typescript copy (Box 22)
      - Reply to Eisenhower Speech of Oct 21, 1952, Boston, Mass., typescript copy, notes, research material (Box 22)
      - Untitled, New Haven, Conn. Oct 25, 1952; draft A, holo.; draft B, typescript copy (Box 22)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 22)
  - Writings of others
    - Bailey, Stephen K. / "Harlan Cleveland, Assistant Secretary of State for International Organization Affairs," reprint, American Oxonian, Apr 1962 (Box 22)
    - Cope, Alfred H. / "Discussion questions in Democratic Citizenship," copyright registration only, 1951; 1953 (Box 22)
    - Foerster, Norman / "Should the Humanities Be Made Human?" Humanities Review, Feb 1947 (Box 22)
    - Hsieh, S.C.: "Problems of Agricultural Development in Asia," outline of a speech before a conference of Peace Corps workers, 1966; typescript (Box 22)
    - Johnson, Gerald W. / Untitled article on the 1960 campaign (Box 22)
    - Keohane, Robert E. / "Historical Method and Primary Sources," reprint, 17th Yearbook of National Council for Social Studies, 1946 (Box 22)
    - "Use of Primary Sources in United States History for High School Pupils," School Review (Box 22)
    - Kulski, W.W. / Foreword to unnamed book (Box 22)
    - Levy, Leonard W. / "Jefferson and Civil Liberties: the Darker Side", repro of typescript rev. (Box 22)
      See also Correspondence: Levy, Leonard W.
    - Payne, Ina Chatterton / "My Greek History Class", typescript (Box 22)
    - Sands, Theodore / "The Unfinished Business of the '52 Campaign: Foreign Policy", typescript copy (Box 22)
    - Whicher, George F. / "Sons of Goliath," American Scholar (Box 22)
- Adlai E. Stevenson material
  - Correspondence, Stuart Gerry Brown, 1955-1964; 3 folders (Box 22)
  - Writings by S.G. Brown
    - Speech for Sen. Mike Monroney, Jun 1960; typescript reproduction (Box 22)
    - re Adlai E. Stevenson, 1960; typescript and typescript copy, repro. (Box 22)
  - Calendar of Collection (Box 22)
  - Interviews with A.E. Stevenson, 1960-1961; typescript and typescript copy, by S.G. Brown (Box 22)
  - Interviews with Political Leaders, Washington, Pennsylvania, New York, 1960-1961; incl holo. typescript and typescript copy by S.G. Brown, correspondence (Box 23)
  - Interviews with Political Leaders, Mid-West, 1960-1961; incl. typescript and typescript copy by S.G. Brown and Robert Lewis Piper (Box 23)
  - Interviews with Political Leaders, California, 1961; holo. typescript and typescript copy by S.G. Brown (Box 23)
  - Confidential reports by Time political writers, typescript reproduction (Box 23)
  - Incoming letters to Stevenson supporting his U-2 Speech, May 1960; repro. (Box 23)
  - Incoming letters to Stevenson opposed to his U-2 Speech, repro. (Box 23)
  - Stevenson fan mail, "Run Again" (Box 23)
  - Stevenson letters, offers of help, repro. (Box 23)
  - New York Politics, repro. of correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 23)
  - Pennsylvania Politics, repro. of correspondence, 1960 (Box 23)
  - California Politics, incl. repro. of correspondence, 1960-1962 (Box 24)
  - Incoming letters to Stevenson regretting his failure to be nominated, repro., 1960 (Box 24)
  - Brown - Stevenson correspondence, 1958-1960 (Box 24)
  - Russell D. Hemenway, New York Office (Box 24)
  - Russell D. Hemenway, correspondence, A-K, 1960; repro. (Box 24)
  - Russell D. Hemenway, correspondence, L-Z, 1960; repro. (Box 24)
  - Stuart Gerry Brown Papers, 1960; incl. draft of speech for Sen. Mike Monroney, typescript rev.; Brown-Monroney conversation, holo.; Brown correspondence (Box 24)
  - John J.B. Shea Papers, 1959-1960; correspondence, repro. (Box 24)
  - John J.B. Shea Papers, Bean and Roper Surveys, 1960; correspondence, repro. (Box 24)
  - Russell D. Hemenway - Washington office (Box 24)
  - Mike Monroney Jr. Papers, 1960; correspondence, repro. (Box 24)
  - John H. Sharon Papers, Jan-Jun 1960; incl. correspondence, repro. (Box 25)
  - John H. Sharon Papers, Jul-Nov 1960; inc. correspondence, repro. (Box 25)
  - James E. Doyle Papers, 1959-1960; typescript copies of memoranda and letters; Brown-Doyle interview, holo. (Box 25)
  - New York draft Group, incl. typescript of interviews by Robert Lewis Piper (Box 25)
  - Missouri draft Groups, 1960-1961; inc. typescript interviews by Robert Lewis Piper, correspondence (Box 25)
  - Miscellaneous draft Groups, 1960-1961; incl. typescript copy interviews; Dictabelt interview; correspondence (Box 25)
  - Los Angeles Convention, incl. typescript copy by Thomas L. Collins (Box 25)
  - Scrapbooks of news clippings about Adlai E. Stevenson 3 volumes, 1961-1962 (Oversize 1)
  - Printed copy of President John F. Kennedy's picture and of his Inaugural Address (Oversize 1)